http://www.emptycartridge.co.uk/privacy-policy

Privacy PolicyCertificates
HomeFund RaisingBulk SupplierWhy Recycle?Pick a CharityFund Raising with usDonate to NI CharityNorthern Ireland Cancer fund for childrenPIPSRecycling for N I HospiceAction Mental HealthDonate to a UK CharityBusinessSchoolsHome UsersCartridges and Mobile phones we accept
Navigation:
HomeFund RaisingBulk SupplierWhy Recycle?Pick a Charity---Fund Raising with us---Donate to NI Charity------Northern Ireland Cancer fund for children------PIPS------Recycling for N I Hospice------Action Mental Health---Donate to a UK CharityBusinessSchoolsHome UsersCartridges and Mobile phones we accept
You Are Here:
HomePrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy We would like to take this opportunity to assure you that we are 100% committed to protecting your privacy and security.Your Personal Information that we may collectIn order to process your enquiry and to provide you with the best possible level of service, we may need to collect some necessary information about you, your name, company name, telephone number and e-mail address. This will only happen when you complete the enquiry form.However, we only use the information we collect about you in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.We will not, under any circumstances, pass any of the information we have collected about you on to any third party. Our commitment to customer service ensures that all personal information is held securely, in accordance with both our internal security policy and the UK Data Protection Act 1998, to ensure that no other party is able to view your details.If you wish to check the information that we hold about you, you can do this at any time by emailing us. If any of the information we hold is inaccurate, we will delete or correct it immediately. Our security procedures mean that we may request proof of identity before we are able to disclose sensitive information to you.EmailingWe do not endorse 'spam' mail - we know how annoying this is! We will send you information that may be relevant to you and we will send regular newsletters to all of our customers. If you choose to do so, you can unsubscribe to these at any point.Cookies StatementOur websites use cookies. A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that we put on your computer. These cookies allow us to distinguish you in anonymous form from other users of our websites and helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our websites. The cookies we use are either 'analytical' cookies, which allow us to recognise and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors move around the sites when they are using them, or functionally necessary for the sites to operate. This helps us to improve the way our websites work, for example, by ensuring that users are finding what they are looking for easily.Some cookies are essential to ensure this website works for you in the best possible way. You may delete and block all cookies from the sites, by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies, but you may not be able to access all or parts of our site.Read more about individual cookies we may use and how to recognise them below.CookieNamePurposeSystem cookiePHPSESSThis cookie is set by our website's back-end system, upon arrival at our website. It is not used by us for any purpose. This cookie is deleted when a user closes their browser.Site cookie acceptancecookiesDirectiveThis cookie is requied to determine if a user has accepted the use of other non-essential cookies on our website.Google Analytics_utma_utmb_utmc_utmzThese cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited. Click here for an overview of privacy at Google
Discover
Login
Register
Contact UsShipping InformationTerms & ConditionsEmpty Inkjet SalesUnused / Surplus CartridgesHolidaysFrequently Asked Questions
Quick Contact
Contact Form
Name:*
Email:*
Confirm Email:*
Telephone:*
Postcode or Acc. No.*:
Enquiry:*
Anti-Spam
Enter the answer to the sum below:
Security
Please tick the box:
Click to Send
Why Recycle?We will pay you for most inkjet cartridges you recycle with us. While doing your bit for the environment, you are also helping out your bank balance at the same time.More Info >Are You A Business?Collecting and recycling your companies used cartridges will save you money on waste disposal, the costs of replacement cartridges and help your company fulfil its Duty of CareMore Info >Are You An Individual?As an individual you can enjoy the benefits of earning additional money by recycling your inkjet cartridges. More Info >
Back to Top
